■ alexandr.baylo@gmail.com | ♠ bailool.github.io | 🖸 BAILOOL | 🛅 abailo

Summary_

Programming Languages: Python (proficient) • C/C++ (proficient) • Java (prior experience) • MatLab (prior experience) Technical skills: Pytorch • Caffe • Tensorflow • OpenCV • LaTeX • Git Languages: Fluent in English, Russian and Ukrainian; Advanced level in Korean.

Experience

Oualcomm MACHINE LEARNING RESEARCHER (SENIOR), XR TEAM Amsterdam, Netherlands

Researching and developing mobile AR and VR enabling technology

AnyVision DEEP LEARNING RESEARCHER AND SCRUM MASTER Belfast, UK

• Body detection and model evaluation tools to understand application scenario

Apr. 2020 - Jun. 2021

• Body re-identification

• Replay face spoofing attack detection

Kakao Brain DEEP LEARNING RESEARCH ENGINEER Seongnam, S.Korea

• Human pose estimation and action similarity research for fitness tracking Nov. 2019 - Mar. 2020

Noul Inc. COMPUTER VISION & DEEP LEARNING RESEARCH ENGINEER Yongin, S.Korea

• Microscopy diagnosis of malaria. Development from training to edge product integration Aug. 2017 - Oct. 2019

• Created hematology analyzer with detection, segmentation, and classification capabilities

• Research on GANs for medical data augmentation resulting in publication

Healthrian SOFTWARE ENGINEER, INTERN Daejeon, S.Korea

• Developed an Android application for ECG medical device Jun. 2015 - Aug. 2015

My Design Lab • KAIST Undergraduate Researcher Daejeon, S.Korea

• Developed a drone to implement wall painting works for skyscrapers Dec. 2014 - Jun. 2015

Education

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Daejeon, S.Korea

Jul. 2021 - present

M.S. IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING. ROBOTICS AND COMPUTER VISION [LAB.] SUPERVISED BY [IN SO KWEON]

Sep. 2015 - Aug. 2017

- A real-time vehicular vision system to seamlessly see-through cars
- Intelligent assistant for people with low vision abilities
- Machine learning-based autonomous vehicle vision system

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Daejeon, S.Korea Sep. 2011 - Aug. 2015

B.S. IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING & BUSINESS AND TECHNOLOGY MANAGEMENT

- Manager at KAIST International Basketball Club (KIBC)
- Vice President, Public Relations Head at KAIST International Student Association (KISA)

Selected Publications

INTERNATIONAL JOURNALS

IJCV22 Real-Time Multi-Car Localization and See-Through System

Access21 A Body Part Embedding Model With Datasets for Measuring 2D Human Motion Similarity

PRL18 Efficient ANMS for homogeneous spatial keypoint distribution

INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCES

CVPRW19 Red blood cell image generation for data augmentation using cGAN

ICCV17 VPGNet: Vanishing Point Guided Network for lane and road marking detection and recognition

WACV17 Robust road marking detection and recognition using density-based grouping and ML techniques